http://www.intercaltg.com/privacy-policy/

Wish list
Track my order(s)
Track my order(s)
Sign inRegister
E-mail
PasswordForgot your password?
Mohair
Curly S-Finish550S/C 3/8+" (10 mm)551S/C 3/8+" (10 mm)300S/C 1/2" (12 mm)325S/C 5/8" (16 mm)325VIS/SC 5/8" (16 mm)785S/C 3/4" (20 mm)785VIS/SC 3/4" (20 mm)610S/C 1-1/2+" (40 mm)690S/C 2+" (52 mm)
MoreCurly-Matted Finish300S/CM 1/2" (12 mm)325S/CM 5/8" (16 mm)785S/CMBH 3/4" (20 mm)830S/CM 1" (25 mm)
Whirl & Wavy Finishes340/WHIRL 5/8" (16 mm)785/WHIRL 3/4" (20 mm)850VIS/WHIRL 1" (25 mm)785VIS/WAVY 3/4" (20 mm)
Vintage Finish785V 3/4" (20 mm)380V 1" (25 mm)850VIS/V 1" (25 mm)
S-Finish300S 1/2" (12 mm)325S 5/8" (16 mm)380S 1" (25 mm)380S/CS 1" (25 mm)830S 1" (25 mm)
Straight270S (4 mm)600S (5 mm)740S 5/8" (16 mm)
KidKID10S/C 1" (25 mm)
Heirloom Finish300H 1/2" (12 mm)325H 5/8" (16 mm)340H 5/8" (16 mm)710H 1" (25 mm)
Tipped325S/CT 5/8" (16 mm)380S/CMT 1" (25 mm)380S/CT 1" (25 mm)
Alpaca
ALP7/S 3/8" (9 mm)ALP6/S 5/8" (16 mm)ALP4/S 1" (25 mm)
German Viscose
VIS1 (6 mm)VIS1/SCM (6 mm)VIS2/SCM (7 mm)VIS3/SC 3/8+" (10 mm)
Synthetics
Orginial Tissavel
Eyes
#500 - Black Glass Eyes#560 - Colored Glass Eyes#218M - Black Matted Glass Eyes#225 - Colored Glass EyesTest Eyes on Steel PinsMemoreyes - Reproduction Shoebutton EyesDoll Eyes - Low LensDoll Eyes - Standard
Other Supplies
100% Virgin Wool FeltAnchor Pearl CottonGuetermann Upholstery ThreadCushing's Perfection Acid Dyes HemostatsDiscsJoint SetsHardwareFingertip Brush and Doll Hair Brush
Sales / Coupons
Home/Intercal's Privacy Policy
Intercal's Privacy Policy
Dear Customer:
Your data is safe with Intercal.
At Intercal we comply with the new GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) legislation, which went into effect on May 25, 2018. The new legislation is securing the processing of your personal data.
Who is processing your personal data?Intercal and our Credit Card Processor (PayPal).
Who can I contact if I have any questions regarding the processing of my personal data?Please feel free to contact Intercal at mohair@intercaltg.com
What is the purpose of the processing of my personal data?We want to stay in contact with our customers/potential customers. We do this by sending you updates, newsletters and and other news of interest. You can opt out at any time.
What categories of personal data is Intercal storing about me?Typically, we store your name, address, e-mail address and phone number. For web orders we do not see your credit card number. This information is transmitted directly to the credit card processor (PayPal). For phone orders, no credit cards are kept on file.
With whom does the company share my data with?Intercal does not share your personal data with anyone outside the company.
For how long does Intercal keep my personal data?We will keep your personal data on file (see 4.) for as long as it is necessary to facilitate the shipment of re-orders. Or....until you make us aware that you do not want us to keep such data on file any longer.
What are my rights?You have the right to (a) get your personal data rectified and/or erased if they are incorrect, (b) be informed about the personal data Intercal is keeping on file about you. As mentioned under 4., this is limited to name, address, e-mail address and phone number.
Please feel free to contact Intercal with your additional questions.
What is Mohair?
What is Alpaca?
Terms, Freight Charges, Information about Canadian and International Orders
2020 Intercal.
